KOBILJON TOSHNAZAROV

1008, 100 High-Tech building Inha-ro, Nam-Gu Incheon South Korea

+8210 5034 2705 kobiljon@nsl.inha.ac.kr qobiljon.github.io

SUMMARY

Expected PhD in Computer Science, expertise in the field of Human-Computer Interaction. Expert software engineer, researcher, and presenter. Most recent research and engineering experience in NSL ¹. Has collaborated with research experts from KAIST, Seoul National University, Yonsei University, INHA University, also with software engineering experts from Samsung Electronics, South Korea. Has professional experience in industry from IUTLab², and ran a club of programmer students at IUT³ during BS degree pursuit.

EDUCATION

- (2020–2023) PhD in Computer Science, Inha University, South Korea
- (2018–2020) MS in Computer Science, Inha University, South Korea, CGPA: 92.7 / 100
- (2014–2018) BS in Computer Science, Inha-IUT, Uzbekistan, CGPA: 84.2 / 100

PUBLICATIONS

- (2020) Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management, CHI'20 Conference Proceedings
- (2020) STDD: Short-Term Depression Detection with Passive Sensing, MDPI Sensors Journal
- (2020) IMSP an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection, KICS'20 Conference Proceedings
- (2019) EasyTrack: Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies, MobiSys'19 Conference Proceedings

EXPERIENCE

- (2019–Present) Research Assistant at NSL
 - Suicidality Prevention with Wearables (passive sensing, digital phenotyping)
 - O Stress / depression / anxiety detection with passive sensing
 - o Digital therapeutics / interventions
 - Abnormal behavior tracking
- (2018–2019) Lecture Assistant at Inha University
 - Application Programming in Java courses
 - Computer Networks courses (link: rb.gy/higlst)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English full professional user (IELTS speaking 8.5 / 9)
- Russian native bilingual user
- Uzbek native bilingual user
- Korean limited user

SKILLS / KEYWORDS

- Hard skills Algorithms, OOP concepts, C++11/17, Java 7/8, Kotlin, Python, C#, SQL, CI/CD, Git, gRPC, Docker
- Soft skills Interpersonal skills, Public speaking, Conceptual thinking, Critical thinking and analysis, Research skills

¹ Networking System's Lab – nsl.inha.ac.kr (Incheon, South Korea)

² IUTLab – iutlab.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)

³ Inha University in Tashkent – inha.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)